

- 574-376-3229
- shilling.jt@gmail.com
- Syracuse, IN 46567

SUMMARY

Sr. Web Developer specializing in front-end. Extensive experience building production websites & interactive web applications.

Consistently turns designs into UI/UX that is responsive, elegant, performant, and pixel perfect.

Adaptable and driven with strong work ethic and motivation to thrive in team-based or individually motivated settings.

SKILLS

JavaScript: Vue/React API: REST & GraphQL

PM: JIRA/Trello

Ops: Webpack/NPM/Babel Git: Github/Gitlab/TFS Agile: Kanban/Scrum

Design: UI/UX/Responsive

PORTFOLIO

www.justinshilling.com

JUSTIN SHILLING

EXPERIENCE

June 2018 - Current

SENIOR FRONT END DEVELOPER Ruoff Mortgage | Fort Wayne, IN

- Lead front-end developer on 15+ public-facing websites & landing pages including flagship website ruoff.com
- Rebuilt & greatly improved UI/UX of several internal interactive web applications using modern technologies like Vue & GraphQL
- Streamlined the front-end development pipeline by modernizing the web stack, solidifying coding standards & conventions, and creating re-usable components & design systems

January 2007 - January 2017

OPERATIONS COORDINATOR Helvey & Associates | Warsaw, IN

- Streamlined administrative processes to effectively reduce department FTE hours during times of cost reduction initiatives
- Coordinated and managed project tasks to ensure completion within established budgets and timelines
- · Managed administrative staff and trained new hires

January 2005 - January 2007

FREELANCE AUDIO ENGINEER Self-employeed | Burbank, CA

 Recorded and mixed audio for solo artists, bands, and commerical voice-overs

EDUCATION

January 2018

Associate of Science | Software Development Ivy Tech Community College, Fort Wayne, IN

- 4.0 GPA
- Summa cum laude graduate

January 2004

Master Recording Program | Audio Engineering Conservatory of Recording Arts & Sciences, Tempe, AZ

• 3.9 GPA